False
b'Times Square right now'
b'UPVOTE so everyone sees we got SUPPORT'
b'GME YOLO update \x97 Jan 28 2021'
b'GME YOLO month-end update \x97 Jan 2021'
b'CLASS ACTION AGAINST ROBINHOOD. Allowing people to only sell is the definition of market manipulation. A class action must be started, Robinhood has made plenty of money off selling info about our trades to the hedge funds to be able to pay out a little for causing people to loose money now'
b'It\x92s treason then'
b"Used some of my GME tendies to buy Nintendo Switches from Gamestop, then donated them to a Children's Hospital. Got featured on the local news and brought glory to WSB."
b'GME YOLO update \x97 Jan 27 2021 --------------------------------------- guess i need 102 characters in title now'
b"IT'S POWER TO THE TRADERS NOW"
b'GME YOLO update \x97 Feb 1 2021'
